你做的
You made it.
你在接受真实采访时就像在精神上精疲力尽
You are as mentally exhausted as you
would be during a real interview,
除了采访者的判断少
except with less judgement
from the interviewer.
开玩笑的我一直都在暗恋你
Just kidding, I've been secretly
judging you all this entire time.
好了现在怎么办
All right, so what now?
结果。
The results.
这些东西都是二进制的
These things are binary.
要么你过去要么你没通过
Either you pass, or you didn't pass.
奇怪的是你可能会失败
Odds are, you're probably gonna fail.
我还是这样说，即便是在这个之后，做了很多很多的采访之后，
I still say this, even after this, even
after doing many, many interviews, and
给了很多很多的面试，我还是说面试是半运气的。
giving many, many interviews,
I still say interviews are half luck.
我的确是这么想的
I do, that's just the way it is.
有时你会在正确的一天得到正确的问题
Sometimes you're just gonna get the right
question on the right day with the right
记者，你就在你的槽里，感觉，我知道。
Interviewer, and you're just in your
groove, feel like, I know this.
我知道如何执行睡眠功能，因为我以前想过这个。
I know how to implement a sleep function
because I've thought about this before.
我知道如何执行扣骨
I know how to implement debounce.
你会得到的
And you'll just have it.
你在你的槽里你知道的感觉很好
You're in your groove and
you know it, and it feels so good.
有时候不是你的一天
Sometimes, it's just not your day.
他们问你关于我们没有掩护的问题
They ask you every
question we didn't cover,
每个你都不可能知道的问题
every question that you
couldn't possibly know.
或者只是个不好的问题，要不你就在上面冻结。
Or it's just a bad question, or
you get up there and you freeze.
没事的你不是失败就是这样
It's okay, you're not a failure,
that happens.
我接受了很多采访
I have failed many interviews,
我的采访可能比我过去的要多了
I've probably failed more
interviews than I've passed.
我已经尽力去了 500 但很困难
I've tried to get to 500 but
yeah, it's tough.
没事的，你是个工程师，这很容易的打击。
It's all right, you're no less of
an engineer, and it's a hard ego blow.
但它会发生在精神上为自己做准备
But it's gonna happen,
just mentally prepare yourself for it.
如果你过去了
And if you pass, hey,
也许我会做一个关于如何谈判你的提议的短期课程
maybe I'll do a short course on
how to negotiate your offer.
这才是最有趣的阶段
That's always the fun phase.
如果你能把你的薪水提高 50 万
When you can increase your
salary by like 50 grand,
如果你很擅长谈判也许还有一些股票期权
maybe more if you're good at negotiating,
maybe some stock options.
也许有个愉快的假期
Maybe some nice vacation time.
那是美好的时光
That's the good times.
这就是你想做的
That's what you wanna get to.
你想要那个积极的压力
You want that positive stress.
如果我能再挤出一万块呢
Like, what if I could squeeze them for
ten grand more?
那是个好时光
That's a good time.
如果你失败了没关系
If you failed, that's okay.
您可以尝试做的是要求反馈。
What you can try to do is ask for
feedback.
很多公司都是有反馈的 cagey ，我觉得是诉讼，
A lot of companies are cagey with
feedback, I think it's a lawsuit thing,
他们不想被起诉什么的
they don't want to get sued or
something like that.
但是希望，如果公司的好处，他们会给你一些反馈。
But hopefully, if the company's good,
they'll give you some feedback.
他们会说你知道吗
They'll say, hey, you know what?
您 aced CSS，您 aced HTML。
You aced CSS, you aced HTML.
您的一些数据结构虽然有点微弱。
Some of your data structure's
though a little weak.
我会回来研究这些的
I would come back and study those.
这是很好的反馈。
That's good feedback.
记住那里有胜利还有学习
Remember, there's winning and
then there's learning.
现在，如果你是记者，你说，嘿，我真的很喜欢这个人。
Now, if you're the interviewer and
you say, hey, I really like this person.
他们太棒了
They were fantastic.
他们不具备我们所期待的知识的深度。
They didn't quite have the depth of
knowledge that we're looking for.
这也会发生
That's gonna happen, too.
不是你面试的人都要经过
Not everybody you interview is gonna pass.
这就是它的发展方式。
That's just the way it goes.
所以作为采访者，我真的鼓励你给出反馈。
So as the interviewer,
I really encourage you to give feedback.
我肯定会鼓励你的
I definitely encourage you.
如果你采访我的团队，你有电话屏幕，我总是写，
If you interview for my team, and you
have the phone screen, I always write up,
需要一段时间，但是我总是写，哎，
it takes a bit of time, but
I always write up, hey,
这才是这个人做的事的好处
here's the pros of what this person did.
这就是他们没有成功的地方
Here's where they didn't succeed as much,
but
欢迎他们回来再再试一次
they're welcome to come back and
try again.
这很有用如果我说不就好了
And that's helpful,
cuz if I just say no, no what?
我没做对吧
What didn't I do right?
这对任何人都没有帮助
That's not helpful to anybody.
如果你真的喜欢他们请他们重新申请
If you really like them,
invite them to reapply.
给他们反馈
Give them feedback.
说哎，你回来工作，我不知道，你的 CSS 有点，我觉得你会
Say hey, if you come back and work on, I
don't know, your CSS a bit, I think you'd
在这个位置上是个王牌，但是我们需要你在那里展示一点更深的深度。
be an ace for this position, but we need
you to show a little bit more depth there.
我认识一个人他们对 Netflix 应用了三次
I know someone,
they applied to Netflix three times.
失败两次，第三次完成。
Failed two times,
got through the third time.
第三次是他们学来的
Third time, they aced it.
我想和那些奉献的人一起工作
That's the kinda people I wanna work with,
people that are dedicated.
就像我说的你一定会失败的
And like I said,
you're probably gonna fail at some point.
没事的没事的
It's okay.
如果你有一个好的经验，一个积极的经验，
If you gave a good experience,
a positive experience, and
你帮他们的时候你帮了他们他们没被人困在任何地方
you were helpful on the way, you helped
them, they didn't get stuck anywhere.
如果他们被困住了你真的帮了他们
If they did get stuck,
you really helped them out.
您邀请他们重新申请。
You invite them to reapply.
工程，特别是前期工程，是一个非常小的世界。
Engineering, especially front engineering,
is a really small world.
我可以扔些名字你可能都在推特上跟他们说
I can throw out some names and
you probably all follow them on Twitter or
因为我们都知道这件事
something like that,
because we all know the same thing.
这是个小宇宙
It's a small universe.
所以别对采访你的人做傻事
So don't be a jerk to people
who are interviewing with you.
你可能会再见到他们他们会记得你的
You will probably see them again and
they'll remember you.
保持联络
And stay in touch.
如果你真的喜欢别人
If you really like someone and
你觉得他们有很大的潜力和他们保持联系
you feel like they have a lot of
potential, stay in touch with them.
每 6 个月说几个话，你要重新申请吗 ?
Reach out every six months to say hey,
you want to reapply?
最糟糕的是你被拒绝了
The worst thing that happens
is you get rejected.
没有成本。
There's no cost.
除了你的自我还没有代价
Other than your ego,
there's no cost to that.
好吧好吧 这就是采访资金的问题。
All right.
So that was interviewing for finance.
大家都做得很好你们都做了
Great job everyone, you all made it.
我们都有点累了
We're all a little tired.
我是个小人有我的绿茶
I'm a little wired, had my green tea.
感觉很好
Feeling good.
但你已经在这一天结束了
But you made it through
the end of the day.
现在我不能保证这些问题
Now, again I can't guarantee
that all these questions
你会看到完美的例子你会看到类似的复制品
you'll see perfectly examples,
you'll see like exact replicas.
但你可能也会看到类似的问题。
But you'll probably see some
similar problems along the way.
如果你遵循如何分解这个问题，它真的很有帮助。
And it really helps if you follow along
how to break down that problem and
试着了解他们想做什么
try to understand what
are they trying to get at.
我想了解这个人的理解
I'm trying to understand this
person understands promises or
他们懂得如何迭代 DOM之类的事情
they understand like how to
iterate the DOM, things like that.
别把重点放在正确的答案上
And don't focus so
much on getting the right answer,
说说你是怎么解决这个问题的
talk about how you got to the solution.
这可能是我给你的最有用的建议
That's probably the most
helpful advice I can give you.
谢谢。
Thank you.
>> [APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; [APPLAUSE]